<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<allinfo>
	<henrydescription>
	&lt;div id=&quot;henrypicture1&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
	
	&lt;span class=&quot;henrypicture1&quot;&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;I was raised in Minnesota by my parents &lt;span class=&quot;bold&quot;&gt;Galina &amp; Peter&lt;/span&gt; along with my one younger sister &lt;span class=&quot;bold&quot;&gt;Elizabeth&lt;/span&gt;.  I grew up in 	&lt;span class=&quot;bold&quot;&gt;St. Paul&lt;/span&gt; but graduated from a high school in Apple Valley.  I joined the 	&lt;span class=&quot;bold&quot;&gt;US Marine Corps&lt;/span&gt; in 2001 and served four years which included two tours in Iraq. After being honorably discharged in 2005, I wanted to continue my education and focus on starting my career. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt; 
	&lt;p&gt;I received a &lt;span class=&quot;bold&quot;&gt;B.S. in Operations Management&lt;/span&gt; from Remington College in San Diego and have worked for technology companies such as &lt;span class=&quot;bold&quot;&gt;THQ&lt;/span&gt; and &lt;span class=&quot;bold&quot;&gt;Microsoft&lt;/span&gt;. I am currently a Mobile Product Manager and get to work with some of the latest mobile technologies. According to &lt;span class=&quot;bold&quot;&gt;Nicole&lt;/span&gt;, my geekiness is very attractive to her so I guess I lucked out. You can be a geek and still get a hot chick.&lt;p&gt;
	&lt;/span&gt;
	</henrydescription>
	
	<nicoledescription>
   &lt;div id=&quot;nicolepicture1&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
		&lt;span class=&quot;nicolepicture1&quot;&gt;	
		&lt;p&gt;	
	I was born and raised in Hawaii by my parents &lt;span class=&quot;bold&quot;&gt;Kathleen&lt;/span&gt; &amp; &lt;span class=&quot;bold&quot;&gt;Craig&lt;/span&gt; along with my sister and brother &lt;span class=&quot;bold&quot;&gt;Jen&lt;/span&gt; &amp; &lt;span class=&quot;bold&quot;&gt;Rick&lt;/span&gt;. Being the youngest and loving attention, I always had a story, song or dance to share.  I graduated from &lt;span class=&quot;bold&quot;&gt;Aiea&lt;/span&gt; High School, then got my bachelor degree in Communication at the &lt;span class=&quot;bold&quot;&gt;University of Hawaii&lt;/span&gt;.  A few years after graduating college, I moved to St Paul, &lt;span class=&quot;bold&quot;&gt;Minnesota&lt;/span&gt; to live with my mom.  I am so glad I did, not only was I lucky enough to find &lt;span class=&quot;bold&quot;&gt;love&lt;/span&gt;, I was able to establish my &lt;span class=&quot;bold&quot;&gt;career&lt;/span&gt;. 
	&lt;/p&gt;	
		&lt;br&gt;
		&lt;p&gt;
	Today, I am in Business Banking and have been with &lt;span class=&quot;bold&quot;&gt;Wells Fargo Bank&lt;/span&gt; since 2006. When I am not working, I enjoy baking cookies &amp; cakes for my coworkers and friends.  I also love to take &lt;span class=&quot;bold&quot;&gt;yoga&lt;/span&gt; classes which I’ve been doing for the last 10 years.  I have two gatos, &lt;span class=&quot;bold&quot;&gt;Oliver&lt;/span&gt; &amp; &lt;span class=&quot;bold&quot;&gt;Bella&lt;/span&gt; and a lovebird named&lt;span class=&quot;bold&quot;&gt; Taj&lt;/span&gt;.
	&lt;/p&gt;			
	&lt;/span&gt;
	</nicoledescription>
	
	<usdescription>
		&lt;div id=&quot;mainStagetext&quot;&gt;
	&lt;p class=&quot;bold&quot;&gt;How we met...&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;It all started back in December of 2005 when I walked into the Apple Valley, Minnesota Sprint Store. I had only been in Minnesota for about two months and was about to start training for my new job. Henry was also on a new adventure in civilian life just being honorably discharged from the United States Marine Corps.  Henry was one of my trainers that day and all I can really remember is constantly laughing with him the entire day. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;According to him, he was immediately smitten by me and made it his personal mission to ask me out. He didn’t exactly have the guts to do it, so he convinced his coworkers to invite me to a concert with him and a few others that weekend. We all went to that concert and had an amazing time!  And very soon after it was clear we were no longer just Nicole or just Henry - we became Nicole &amp; Henry, a couple, best buddies, two peas in a pod &amp; now life long partners.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Big thank you to &lt;a href=&quot;http://leilapeterson.com/&quot;&gt;Leila Peterson&lt;/a&gt; for taking such beautiful pictures.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id=&quot;gallery&quot;&gt;

		&lt;div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
		&lt;div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
		&lt;div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
		&lt;div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
		&lt;div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
		&lt;div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
		&lt;div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
		&lt;div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
		&lt;div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
		&lt;div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;
	</usdescription>
	
	<weddingdescription>
	 Details are coming very soon.
	</weddingdescription>
</allinfo>


